bikiniriot.com 2009-06-22

# Bikini Riot Privacy Policy

_**Privacy Policy**_

BIKINIRIOT.COM (the "Site") is committed to protecting your privacy. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. By registering for access and using our Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not use our Site.

**Notification of Changes  
**We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on this page. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use our Site, we encourage you to check this page regularly. If you continue to access or use our Site after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use  
**We may log user information when signing onto or using the Site, including but not limited to IP address, URL of the Web page user was on before visiting the Site, user's browser version, user's registration forms, surveys, cookie data, and communications transmitted through applications on the Site. We reserve the right to use this information to increase the users.

**Cookies  
**A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We may use cookies to track affiliate sales and referring URL's. In order to provide better functionality to our users, our site may employ cookies to help us identify popular areas of our Site, improve our Site, personalize services for members and collect aggregate site statistics.

**Sharing  
**Any and all information collected on this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned to any third parties. However, we reserve the right to transfer collected information to a third party as a result of a sale or acquisition, merger or bankruptcy involving Company. 

**Law Enforcement  
**We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. Examples of such cooperation include compliance with discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders and writs.

**Links  
**Our Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our Site they should read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Security  
**We do not and will not in the future keep sensitive billing information on our local servers. Our billing processor, CCBill.com, will keep this information. Please see https://support.ccbill.com/ for our billing processor's privacy policy.

**Choice  
**BIKINIRIOT.COM may use your email address to send registered and former registered users e-mail, e-mail newsletters, Site news updates, or other notices regarding new services, promotions, or other information which we deem may be of general interest.. Users who no longer wish to receive materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by contacting us at info@bikiniriot.com. We will comply with all requests for removal.

**Contact Information  
**If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you otherwise need to contact us regarding your personally identifiable information, contact us by sending an email to: info@bikiniriot.com.
